(Sheldon:)Well, they can't cancel it.
It ended on a cliffhanger.
Well, they did.
(Penny:)There are two dumplings left.
Want them?
(Sheldon:)Dumplings? Don't you understand
what's going on here?
(Penny:)As a rule, no.
(Sheldon:)That show ended with all the residents
of New York either dead or unconscious.
(Sheldon:)Now I'll never know what happened.
(Penny:)Why don't you make up
your own ending?
(Sheldon:)Oh. Sure, what a wonderful idea.
(Sheldon:)And after that I'll make up my own rules
of oral hygiene...
...and instead of flossing,
I'll rub pudding on my gums.
I'm gonna get the number of
the Syfy Channel and give them what for.
(Leonard:)Oh, please don't do that.
(Sheldon:)No. They can't just cancel
a show like Alphas.
(Sheldon:)They have to help the viewers let go.
(Sheldon:)Firefly did a movie to wrap things up.
(Sheldon:)Buffy the Vampire Slayer
continued on as a comic book.
(Sheldon:)Heroes gradually lowered the quality
season by season...
...until we were grateful it ended.
(Penny:)I feel bad for whoever gets that phone call.
Ah, don't. If they didn't wanna be
yelled at by crazy nerds...
(Leonard:)...they shouldn't have started
a sci-fi channel.